Guide to the Leo Bogart Papers, 1912-2010 and undated RL.10146
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Professional Series, 1914-2005 and undated, 84 boxes
  - Newspaper Advertising Bureau (NAB) Subseries, 1914-1990 and undated
    - Major projects (Box 29)
      - Newspaper Readership Project (NRP), 1965-1984
        - Programs and research
          - Black readership
            - Presentation materials, 1976-1980 (Box 33)
            - Questionnaire, 1982-1983 (Box 33)
          - Clippings and notes, 1972-1986 and undated (Box 33)
          - Circulation Computer Systems symposia, 1979-1980 (Box 33)
          - Editors Look at the Daily Newspaper: A Mail Survey, 1977-1978 (Box 33)
          - Editors workshops, 1980-1982 (Box 33)
          - Education
            - Empire State College Circulation Management Program materials, 1976-1984 (Box 33)
            - Proposal for a Graduate-Level Program in Circulation Management, 1977-1978 (Box 33)
          - Evaluating editorial content proposal, 1977 (Box 33)
          - Front page study correspondence, 1977 (Box 33)
          - Issues workshops, 1982-1983 (Box 33)
          - National Newspaper Week correspondence, 1981 (Box 33)
          - Newspaper design materials, 1980 (Box 33)
          - The Newspaper Fund correspondence, 1981 (Box 33)
          - Newsprint Information Committee study, 1976-1977 (Box 34)
          - Newspaper Research Council Mining Company project correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 34)
          - Project Readership in 1980 program, 1976 (Box 34)
          - Proposals, 1978-1983 and undated (Box 34)
          - Readership committee survey, 1980-1981 (Box 34)
          - Research summaries, 1979 (Box 34)
          - Research reports
            - Circulation and Home Delivery Patterns, 1983 (Box 34)
            - Newspaper Pages, Ads and Readers 1984 (Box 34)
          - Research workshop, 1978 (Box 34)
          - Start Your Own Newspaper project, 1977-1982 (Box 34)
          - 3 to Get Ready supplement correspondence, 1975-1979 (Box 34)
          - Women's seminar, 1979 (Box 34)
          - The World of the Working Journalist study and commentary, 1982 (Box 34)
          - Youth readership seminar, 1977-1979 (Box 34)
        - Publications
          - Newspaper Readership Project: An Overview and Catalog of Materials, 1977-1983, 1983 (Box 34)
          - Children, Mothers and Newspapers, 1978 (Box 34)
          - Circulation: Key to Successful Newspaper Marketing, 1982 (Box 34)
          - Fifteen Case Histories in Circulation Management, 1982 (Box 34)
          - How to Have Fun and Profit From Reading Newspapers, 1979 (Box 34)
          - Instructional booklets, 1982 and undated (Box 34)
          - Making Connections: The Art of Cold Call Subscription Selling, 1978 (Box 34)
          - Newspaper inserts, 1977-1979 (Box 34)
          - Newspaper Readership Project in the U.K. reports, 1981-1982 (Box 34)
          - Promotional brochures, 1977-1983 and undated, 2 folders (Box 35)
          - Research Note articles, 1981-1982 (Box 35)
          - Sales and the Single Copy, 1983 (Box 35)
          - Stop the Stops: Handing Customer Complaints, undated (Box 35)
          - Television Supervisor's Survival Kit, 1979 (Box 35)
        - Speeches
          - 1976-1983 and undated, speeches by others (Box 35)
          - 1978 July 7, ICMA convention speech (Box 35)
          - 1979 May, ASNE convention presentation (Box 35)
          - 1979, Newspapers in Transition, ANPA (Box 35)
          - 1980 Mar. 28 Newspaper in Education program development conference speech (Box 35)
          - 1981 July 13, ICMA convention speech (Box 35)
          - 1982 Nov. 10, What Have We Learned from the Newspaper Readership Project?, APME (Box 35)
          - 1983 Jan., INAME conference report (Box 35)
          - 1983 Apr. 26, ANPA convention report (Box 35)
          - 1983 May 9, How Do Your Papers Rate with Readers?, ASNE (Box 35)
          - 1983 May 17, INPA convention report (Box 35)
          - 1983 June 21, ICMA sales conference report (Box 35)
          - 1983 Aug. 8, AEJMC convention report (Box 35)
      - Future of Advertising Project, 1973-1989 (Box 36)
        - Administrative
          - A.A.A.A. recommendations, 1986 (Box 36)
          - Advertising's Next Quarter Century correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 36)
          - Budget materials, 1985-1988 (Box 36)
          - General correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box 36)
          - Recommendation adoption correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 36)
        - Meetings and conferences
          - 1983 Oct. 24-26, The Future of Advertising Tarrytown conference (Box 36)
          - 1984 May 20, Southern Newspaper Publishers Association conference (Box 36)
          - 1985 July 28-31, INAME sales conference (Box 36)
          - 1985 Oct. 16, Oregonian Research Symposium (Box 36)
          - 1985 Nov. 6, Association of Canadian Advertisers conference (Box 36)
          - 1986 Oct. 28-29, ANPA Circulation & Readership committee meeting (Box 36)
          - ANA board meetings, 1986-1988 (Box 36)
          - 1987 July 8, Los Angeles meeting (Box 36)
          - 1987-1988, NASC committee (Box 36)
          - 1988 Apr. 5, Editors/creatives meeting (Box 36)
        - Publications
          - Advertising and Circulation Rates, 1987 (Box 36)
          - Guide to Quality Newspaper Reproduction 1986 (Box 36)
          - Guidelines for Standardized Retail Research, 1986 (Box 36)
          - Major Assumptions and Predictions to the Year 2000, 1985 (Box 36)
          - Opportunities in National Advertising through Simplified Rate Structures, 1986-1987 (Box 36)
          - Publication catalogs, 1988 (Box 36)
          - Publisher Survey on Newspaper Practices, 1986 (Box 36)
          - Readers: How to Gain and Retain Them, 1986 (Box 36)
          - Standard Market Data Folder, 1987 (Box 36)
          - The Structure of Newspaper Advertising Sales, 1987 (Box 36)
          - An Update on Readership, 1987-1989 (Box 36)
        - Research
          - The Future of Advertising to the Year 2010 Delphi survey, 1983-1984 (Box 36)
          - National Advertising in Daily Newspapers study, 1984-1985 (Box 37)
          - National advertising study proposals, 1984 (Box 37)
          - Membership survey, 1986 (Box 37)
          - Publishers surveys, 1985-1987 (Box 37)
          - Recommendation adoption survey, 1988 (Box 37)
        - Speeches
          - 1979 Sept., The Future of Advertising, Board of Directors meeting (Box 37)
          - 1984 Mar. 5, ARF conference report (Box 37)
          - 1984 Mar. 27, Motor City publishers' meetings speeches (Box 37)
          - 1985-1986, Board of Directors reports (Box 37)
          - 1986 Apr. 22, ANPA convention presentation (Box 37)
          - 1986 July 1, ICMA conference report (Box 37)
          - 1986 July 29, INAME conference report (Box 37)
          - 1986 Oct. 6, SNPA report (Box 37)
          - 1986 Dec., ANPA board report (Box 37)
          - 1987 Jan. 27, INAME conference report (Box 37)
          - 1987 May 20, INMA conference speech (Box 37)
          - 1987 Dec. 31, Thoughts on the Future of the 'Future of Advertising' (Box 37)
          - 1988 Jan. 24, INAME conference report (Box 37)
          - 1988 Apr. 15, An Update on Readership, ASNE (Box 37)
          - 1988 Apr. 26, ANPA convention presentation (Box 37)
          - 1988 May 23, INFE conference report (Box 37)
          - 1989 Jan. 23, INAME conference report (Box 37)
        - Task force files
          - General files
            - Future of Advertising committee correspondence, 1978-1985 (Box 37)
            - Future of Advertising committee correspondence, 1978-1985, 2 folders (Box 38)
            - Future of Advertising committee mailings, 1985 (Box 38)
            - Steering committee, 1985-1988
              - Mailing to committee members, 1985 (Box 38)
              - Meeting minutes, 1985-1988, 2 folders (Box 38)
            - Future of Advertising task forces, 1985-1988 and undated
              - Correspondence, 1988 and undated (Box 38)
              - Member lists, 1985-1988 and undated (Box 38)
          - Alternate Distribution task force, 1985-1987
            - Correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 38)
            - Meeting minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 38)
            - Shared mail survey, 1985-1986 (Box 38)
            - Total market coverage proposals, 1986 (Box 38)
          - Classified task force, 1985-1989
            - Clippings, 1986 and undated (Box 38)
            - Correspondence, 1986-1989, 2 folders (Box 38)
            - Meeting minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 38)
            - New technology study, 1987 (Box 38)
            - Poynter Institute correspondence, 1987 (Box 38)
            - Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 38)
            - Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 39)
            - Research studies, 1986-1987 and undated (Box 39)
          - Marketing Data task force, 1983-1989 and undated
            - Correspondence, 1985-1989 (Box 39)
            - Guidelines for standardization correspondence, 1985-1989 (Box 39)
            - Meeting minutes, 1984-1986 (Box 39)
            - Proposals, 1983-1986 and undated (Box 39)
          - Pricing & Positioning task force, 1978-1989 and undated
            - Clippings, 1978-1986 (Box 39)
            - Correspondence, 1985-1989, 2 folders (Box 39)
            - Meeting minutes, 1985-1989, 2 folders (Box 39)
            - Pricing subcommittee, 1986-1987 (Box 39)
            - Proposals, 1985-1987 (Box 39)
            - Rate structure proposal, 1986-1987 (Box 40)
            - Reports, 1986-1987 and undated (Box 40)
          - Promotion & Advertising task force, 1985-1989 and undated
            - Clippings, 1985-1986 (Box 40)
            - Correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box 40)
            - Gridiron Club correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 40)
            - Magazine proposal, 1987-1988 (Box 40)
            - Meeting minutes, 1985-1986 and undated (Box 40)
            - Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 40)
          - Readership task force, 1984-1988 and undated
            - Circulation survey, 1985-1986 (Box 40)
            - Clippings, 1984-1987 and undated (Box 40)
            - Correspondence, 1985-1988, 2 folders (Box 40)
            - Meeting minutes, 1985-1988 (Box 40)
            - Notes, 1986-1988 (Box 40)
            - Questionnaires, 1988 (Box 40)
            - Reports, 1986-1988 and undated (Box 40)
          - Sales Personnel & Training task force, 1985-1987 and undated
            - Clippings, 1986-1987 and undated (Box 40)
            - Correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 41)
            - Meeting minutes, 1985-1987 and undated (Box 41)
            - New York Times meeting materials, 1986 (Box 41)
            - Proposals, 1986 (Box 41)
            - Towers, Perring, Forster & Crosby reports, 1986-1987 and undated (Box 41)
          - Sales Structure task force, 1983-1988 and undated
            - Clippings, 1983-1985 (Box 41)
            - Correspondence, 1985-1988, 2 folders (Box 41)
            - Management committee, 1985-1987 (Box 41)
            - Meeting minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 41)
            - Reports, undated (Box 42)
          - Standardization task force, 1985-1989 and undated
            - Clippings, 1985-1987 (Box 42)
            - Correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 42)
            - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 42)
            - Meeting minutes, 1985-1988, 3 folders (Box 42)
            - Reports, 1986-1989 and undated (Box 42)
          - Quality/Color task force, 1985-1987
            - Correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 42)
            - Meeting minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 42)
  - Professional Service Subseries, 1948-1991 and undated
    Documents Bogart's membership and service in professional organizations and clubs and on committees and advisory boards. Arranged alphabetically.
    - AAPOR (Box 43)
      - Comments on "AAPOR History," 1948-1990 (Box 43)
      - Correspondence, 1962-1996 (Box 43)
      - New York Times letter to editor, 1969 (Box 43)
      - Census Director nomination, 1973 (Box 43)
      - Code of Ethics correspondence, 1967-1987 (Box 43)
      - Monitoring public opinion project, 1978-1979 (Box 43)
      - Programs and directories, 1956-1970 (Box 43)
      - Public Opinion Quarterly advisory correspondence, 1979-1989 (Box 43)
    - AMA
      - EFFIE awards, 1970-1987 (Box 43)
      - General correspondence, 1962-1981 (Box 43)
    - American Advertising Federation
      - Advertising Hall of Fame nomination, 1986-1987 (Box 43)
      - Advertising self-regulation proposal, 1971 (Box 43)
      - General correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 43)
    - ANPA
      - ANPA Brands TV's Figures False, 1967 (Box 43)
      - Bureau of Advertising committee, 1967-1970 (Box 43)
      - Circulation and Readership Committee, 1977-1988 (Box 43)
      - General correspondence, 1977-1988 (Box 43)
      - Industry Affairs committee, 1982-1984 (Box 43)
      - Minorities task force, 1987-1988 (Box 43)
      - News and editorial content study summary, 1973 (Box 43)
      - News Research Center, 1969-1979 (Box 43)
      - News Research committee, 1976-1982 (Box 43)
      - Newspaper in Education committee, 1974-1989 (Box 43)
    - APA correspondence, 1971-1983 (Box 43)
    - APA Consumer Psychology Division
      - APA and New York Bar Association joint meeting, 1971-1972 (Box 43)
      - Fellowship committee correspondence, 1961-1976 (Box 43)
      - General correspondence, 1961-1976 (Box 44)
      - Legal Applications of Consumer Psychology committee, 1971-1972 (Box 44)
    - APA Society for Psychological Study of Social Issues
      - General correspondence, 1964-1971 (Box 44)
      - Man in Space Group, 1956-1960 (Box 44)
    - ARF, 1965-1989 (Box 44)
    - ASA correspondence, 1962-1987 (Box 44)
    - ASNE correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 44)
    - ABC
      - Data Bank, 1973 (Box 44)
      - General correspondence, 1971-1988 (Box 44)
      - Tommaney Plan, 1971 (Box 44)
    - Center for Applied Linguistics, 1984-1989 (Box 44)
    - Commission on Reading Trends in the U.S. advisory group, 1979 (Box 44)
    - Consumer Behavior Abstracts editorial board, 1971 (Box 44)
    - INAME
      - General correspondence, 1967-1989 (Box 44)
      - Schools and Colleges committee, 1977-1989 (Box 44)
    - INPA correspondence, 1987 (Box 44)
    - Institute of International Education correspondence, 1983 (Box 44)
    - Intercorporate luncheon group contact list, undated (Box 44)
    - International Association for Mass Communication Research correspondence, 1974-1975 and undated (Box 44)
    - Journal of Communication reviews, 1979-1988 (Box 44)
    - Marcel Dassault Foundation, 1974 (Box 44)
    - Market Research Council, 1964-1987 (Box 44)
    - National Association for the Prevention of Addiction to Narcotics, 1971 (Box 44)
    - Overseas Press Club
      - General correspondence, 1960-1985 and undated (Box 44)
      - Newsman survey, 1966-1967 (Box 44)
    - Radio and Television Research Council materials, 1954-1963 (Box 44)
    - Social Science Research Council
      - General correspondence, 1977-1989 (Box 44)
      - Mass Communication and Political Behavior committee, 1977-1989 (Box 44)
      - 1976 elections committee, 1974 (Box 44)
      - TV Entertainment conference, 1976 (Box 45)
      - TV and Social Behavior committee, 1975-1979 (Box 45)
    - Society for the Study of Symbolic Interaction, 1974-1975 (Box 45)
    - WAPOR
      - Future of World Association for Public Opinion Research conference packet, 1982 (Box 45)
      - General correspondence, 1965-1983 (Box 45)
      - de Miguel, Armando, 1971 (Box 45)
      - Project Camelot, 1965-1966 (Box 45)
      - Standards, 1966 (Box 45)
    - Wilson Center Media Studies Project advisory committee
      - Advisory committee, 1987-1990 (Box 45)
      - Coverage of the War in the Gulf seminar, 1991 (Box 45)
  - Research Files Subseries, 1947-2005 and undated
    Consists of clippings, writings, and notes on various subjects that Bogart maintained for reference and as source material for his writings, speeches, and research. Arranged alphabetically by topic.
    - A.C. Neilsen program type comparisons from 1950-1988, 1989 (Box 46)
    - Advertising and marketing
      - Advertising and marketing, 1973-2000 and undated (Box 46)
      - Crisis in advertising, 2001-2004 and undated (Box 46)
    - Anthropology, 1974-1992 (Box 46)
    - Bibliographic and library search materials
      - Bibliographies, circa 1950-2000 (Box 46)
      - CLIO database search for materials on patronage, 1989 (Box 46)
      - Library search results for materials on high and low culture, 1989 (Box 46)
    - Blacks, 1975-1977 and undated (Box 46)
    - Book titles, 1990-1992 and undated (Box 46)
    - Books, 1975-2004 and undated (Box 46)
    - The Emerging Landscape Presstime newspaper readership map, 1998 (Box 46)
    - Focus groups, 1976-2000 and undated (Box 46)
    - Harper's Magazine dispute, 1971 (Box 46)
    - Health, 2005 (Box 46)
    - The Internet, 1997-2003 and undated, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - Journalism, circa 1975-1995 (Box 47)
    - Literacy, circa 1975-1986 (Box 47)
    - Magazines, 1998-2002 and undated (Box 47)
    - Metro controversy, 1999-2000 (Box 47)
    - Marketing News: The 1992 Honomichl Business Report on the Marketing Research Industry, 1992 (Box 47)
    - Mass media
      - Changes, 1981 and undated (Box 47)
      - Consolidation, 1999-2003 and undated (Box 47)
      - Control of information, 1960-1976 and undated (Box 47)
      - Labeling media content, 2000-2004 and undated, 2 folders (Box 47)
      - Mass media, 1967-2004 and undated, 3 folders (Box 47)
      - Mass media, 1967-2004 and undated, 3 folders (Box 48)
      - Ratings, 1997-1998 and undated (Box 48)
      - Sex, 2004 (Box 48)
    - Movie industry, 1958-2004 and undated (Box 48)
    - Music industry, 2000-2003 (Box 48)
    - News coverage, 1967-1996 and undated, 4 folders (Box 48)
    - Newspapers
      - Competition, 1973-1990 (Box 48)
      - Newspapers, 1947-2004 and undated (Box 48)
      - Newspapers, 1947-2004 and undated, 7 folders (Box 49)
      - Newspapers and the Internet 1992-2000 and undated (Box 50)
      - Can newspapers be saved?, 1989-2005 and undated (Box 50)
    - Obituaries, 1989-1997 (Box 50)
    - Pamplona trip, 1982 (Box 50)
    - Polls, politics, and public opinion, 1966-1997 and undated, 4 folders (Box 50)
    - Propaganda, 2001-2005 (Box 50)
    - Research studies, 1983-2004 and undated (Box 50)
    - Russia and Eastern Europe
      - Post-Soviet press, 1991-1992 (Box 50)
      - Public opinion, 1961-1963 and undated (Box 50)
    - SATs and reading, 1975 (Box 50)
    - Scholarly publishing, 2004, 3 folders (Box 51)
    - Technology, 1972-2004 and undated, 2 folders (Box 51)
    - Television
      - Broadcast cable, 1969-2004 and undated, 2 folders (Box 51)
      - Digital cable, 1998, 2 folders (Box 51)
      - Effects on behavior, 1976-1990 (Box 51)
      - News, 1973-1978 and undated (Box 51)
      - Television, 1960-1989 and undated, 4 folders (Box 52)
      - V-chip, 2001-2003 and undated (Box 52)
      - Violence, 1970-2000 and undated, 5 folders (Box 52)
    - Vietnam war, 1968-1971 and undated (Box 53)
    - Video games, 2001-2004 (Box 53)
    - Youth, 1966-2003 and undated (Box 53)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Articles and clippings, 1952-2004 and undated, 1-8 of 27 folders (Box 53)
      - Articles and clippings (continued), 1952-2004 and undated, 9-24 of 27 folders (Box 54-55)
      - Articles and clippings (continued), 1952-2004 and undated, 25-27 of 27 folders (Box 56)
      - Ephemera, 1980-1982 and undated (Box 56)
      - Journals and printed publications, 1950-2005, 1-5 of 11 folders (Box 56)
      - Journals and printed publications (continued), 1950-2005, 6-11 of 11 folders (Box 57)
      - Books
        - Il Faut Nous Faire Soigner! by Claude Monnier, 2002 (Box 57)
        - Jews in the News: British and American Newspaper Articles About Jews, 1665-1800 by Herman J. Obermayer, 2002 (Box 57)
  - Writings and Speeches Subseries, 1943-2004 and undated
    Documents 149 speeches; 195 published articles; 14 books; book chapters and contributions; and other written materials Bogart produced over his career. Also includes articles for a monthly column in Presstime that Bogart wrote from 1989-2005. The subseries is divided in five sections: Speeches, Articles, Books, Book chapters and contributions, and Unpublished writings and drafts. For speeches that directly report on Newspaper Advertising Bureau activities, see the Newspaper Advertising Bureau (NAB) Subseries. Writings are arranged chronologically by date of publication, or for unpublished writings, creation date. Speeches are arranged chronologically by date of delivery.
    - Speeches (Box 58)
      - 1954-1966 and undated, miscellaneous early speeches (Box 58)
      - 1955 Apr. 14, A Study of the Operating Assumptions of the U.S. Information Agency, AAPOR (Box 58)
      - 1955 May 12, How Media Research Helps Produce More Effective Advertising, AMA (Box 58)
      - 1955 June 24, How Media Research Helps Produce More Effective Advertising, Continuing Clinic of Agency Operations (Box 58)
      - 1955 Dec. 8, Magazines in the TV Era, AMA (Box 58)
      - 1956 Mar. 16, What We Do and Don't Know About Advertising Research, Advertising Club of Minneapolis (Box 58)
      - 1956 May 8, Magazines in the Postwar Era, Magazine Publishers Association (Box 58)
      - 1956 Sept. 13, Television as a News Medium, ESOMAR (Box 58)
      - 1956 Nov. 27, How to Plan Media Strategy: Summation and Critique, AAAA (Box 58)
      - 1957 Apr. 10, Advertising and the Hardware Industry, Southern Hardware Convention (Box 58)
      - 1958 Jan. 3, Media and the Market, AMA (Box 58)
      - 1958 May 5-9, The Impact of Television, Radio in the Future of Canada conference, University of British Columbia (Box 58)
      - 1958 Oct. 27, AAAA conference speech (Box 58)
      - 1959 June 19, AMA panel discussion on Marketing Keys to Profits in the 1960s (Box 58)
      - 1960 Mar. 29, Newspapers in the Sixties, Cincinnati Council of the AAAA (Box 58)
      - 1960 Oct. 17, A New Look at the Beer Market, National Beer Wholesalers Association (Box 58)
      - 1960 Oct. 18, The Measurement of Advertising Effectiveness: Some Reflections on a Problem, AMA (Box 58)
      - 1960, General Electric seminar notes (Box 58)
      - 1961 Apr. 21, Marketing Research and Marketing Management, AMA (Box 58)
      - 1961 Oct. 10, Cost Per Thousand Revisited, AMA (Box 58)
      - 1962 Jan. 12, Commentary on Dr. Winick's Paper, AMA panel discussion (Box 58)
      - 1962 May 12, The Research Project: From Conception to Presentation, Market Research Trade Association (Box 58)
      - 1962 Aug. 31, Social System and Process in the Utilization of Marketing Research, ASA (Box 58)
      - 1963 Oct. 15, Reflections on the Computer in Advertising, American Association of Newspaper Representatives (Box 58)
      - 1964 May 14, The Advertising Explosion and its Repercussions on Communication, AMA (Box 58)
      - 1964 June 24, The Concept of the Audience in American Communication Research, IAMCR (Box 58)
      - 1965 Jan. 13, Ten Vital Facts About Newspapers and What They Mean to the Retail Merchant, NRMA (Box 59)
      - 1965 Feb. 3, New Directions for Psychology in Advertising, Psychology in Media Strategy Symposium, AMA (Box 59)
      - 1965 Apr. 27, A Second Look at Intermedia Comparisons, National Newspaper Promotion Association (Box 59)
      - 1965 May 18, untitled speech on the marketing concept (Box 59)
      - 1965 May 20, World Public Opinion and the Research Profession, WAPOR (Box 59)
      - 1965 June 14-16, Psychology, Computers, and Media Research, AMA (Box 59)
      - 1965 Sept., What Research for the Smaller Newspaper?, INAE (Box 59)
      - 1966 Jan. 20, How Newspapers Will Tell Media Men More!, INAE (Box 59)